Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
- Retail Clerks International Association (RCIA), Publication (Box 318, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Fair Play, 1952; Publication (Box 318, Folder 10)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 17
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the arbitration between Local 125, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), A.F.L.-C.I.O. and the Quaker Oats Company: brief for the company, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: In the matter of the arbitration between New York Medical College, Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospitals, and Local 1199, Drug and Hospital Employees Union affiliated with RWDSU, AFL-CIO Hospital Division: Opinion and award, 1964; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: In the matter of the arbitration between Clara Maass Memorial Hospital and Local 1199, Drug & Hospital Employees Union: Opinion and award, 1964; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: In the matter of the arbitration between Beth Israel Hospital, Employer and Local 1199, Drug & Hospital Employees Union, R.W.S.D.U., Union: Award and arbitrator, 1963; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: In the matter of the arbitration between Local 1199, Drug & Hospital Employees Union, RWSDU, Union and Jewish Home & Hospital for the Aged, Employer: Award and arbitrator, 1965; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: In the matter of the arbitration between New York Medical College, Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospitals, and Local 1199, Drug and Hospital Employees Union affiliated with RWDSU, AFL-CIO Hospital Division, 1964; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: In the matter of the arbitration between Clara Maass Memorial Hospital and Local 1199, Drut & Hospital Employees Union, 1965; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: In the matter of the arbitration between Beth Israel Hospital and Local 1199, Drug & Hospital Employees Union, RWSDU, 1965; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: In the matter of the arbitration between Local 1199, Drug & Hospital Employees Union, RWDSU and Jewish Home & Hospital for the aged, 1965; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The store workers security plan, 1956; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: The 65 Pension plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The 65 Security Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The 65 Security Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Labor Health Institute, Inc.: quality of service, 1948; Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry G. Farish
  - Item 15: What happens to your union dollars?, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Take care of your teeth, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: LHI - Service when you need it, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
    Notes: Flyer. 2 Copies
  - Item 18: Protect your family's health, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Your health, a manual for the members of the, Publication (Box 319, Folder 1)
- Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU). Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Employees Union (New York, N.Y.), Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the arbitration between Bloomingdale Brothers, Inc. and Local 3, United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, C.I.O. and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, C.I.O., 1945; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Labor Health Insitute is on its way., Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Aims and purposes of the Labor Health Institute, 1946; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
    Author: Elmer Richman
  - Item 4: The Labor Health Institute - a plan for health service, 1946; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Labor sponsored health plans, 1946; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: LHI - Labor Health Institute, Inc. --- chart, Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: 1975 National Pension Fund, Annual report, Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: 1199 Dental program, Prescription program, 1975; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: National Benefit Fund for Hospital and Health Care Employees - Directory of Participating Pharmacies, New York, New Jersey, Connecticut - Prescription Plan, Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Blue Cross Prescription Program - Local 1-S/Macy's Retirees, 1974; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Full and Part-Time Employees Health Plan improvements - Local 1-S/Macy's, 1974; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The Health Plan sponsored by Local 1-S, 1971; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: The Local 1199 Benefit plan, 1975; Publication (Box 319, Folder 2)
- Hotel and Club Employees Union, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your insurance plan, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Hotel and Club Employees Union, Local 6, AFL-CIO --packet, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Esta es su Union: bienvenidos al Local 6, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: como y donde buscar un empleo, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Organizing wholesale; annual message before opening session of general executive board ... March 14, 1938, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
    Author: Arthur Osman
  - Item 6: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 319, Folder 3)
    Author: New York Hotel Trades Council; Hotel Association of New York City
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Shop steward manual, Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Twenty Five years of progress - 1939-1964, Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 65 security plan: the first 10 years, 1955; Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The 65er. " '65' Convention Maps the road", 1962; Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.18 (1962)
  - Item 5: The 65 Pension Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Know anyone who needs a good union?, 1956; Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: 6th Biennial Convention - Officers report, 1954; Publication (Box 319, Folder 4)
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Avery formula, 1944; Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The store workers security plan, 1956; Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: el plan de Seguro del 65, 1954; Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: District 65--Applicant's Book, Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Retired member's activity calendar, August, 1956, Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Tenants the law does protect you, Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The money-saving services of District 65, 1956; Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Quarterly report of Security plan, 1959; Publication (Box 319, Folder 5)
    Notes: April, May, June 1959
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution: District 65, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union affiliated with Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Report on unsettled contracts, 1957; Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The 65 Security Plan Pension Fund,--Effective Feb. 1, 1950 as amended Effective Feb. 1, 1957, 1950-1957 (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Unions and their Senior Citizens., Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
    Notes: Reprinted from Industrial Bulletin. 2 copies
  - Item 5: Quarterly report of Security plan, 1959; Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Security plan - Quarterly report, 1955; Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
    Notes: May, 1955
  - Item 7: Annual '65' reports on security, pension plans, 1958; Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: flyers - Retail Shoe Employees Union Local 1268; District 65 Credit Union; The Store Workers Retirement Plan; The Senior 65er's activity calendar; Local 1-s is your union!, Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Arnold Constable Unfair - An open letter to the public, Publication (Box 319, Folder 6)
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: to Build '65', Publication (Box 319, Folder 7)
- Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America. District 65, Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Like a beautiful child: the most widely discussed film ever produced by a labor union (article), 1967; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The store workers security plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The 65 Pension plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The 65 Security Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Senior 65er, 1960; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
    Notes: 10th Anniv. Issue (May 1960)
  - Item 6: Israel, Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Union-Made film evokes emotional response, 1967; Publication (Box 319, Folder 8)
    Notes: Article. Reprint from the New York Times